Recreational Services and Athletics fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Publication and publicity records, 1960 - 1995; F-80-9; 81 cm of textual records
  - [Simon Fraser University: A Winning Tradition], [ca 1980] - [ca 1989]; F-80-9-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Women's Fall Sports Program], 1991; F-80-9-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Simon Fraser University: Athletic and Recreational Services, Physical Development Centre, Program and Information], 1973 - 1982; F-80-9-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Recreation: intramural and club programs], 1967 - 1990; F-80-9-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 80-20)
  - [Outdoor Program: collected file], 1967 - 1974; F-80-9-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 80-20)
  - [SFU Fitness Newsletters], 1980 - 1985; F-80-9-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 80-20)
  - [Recreation programs], 1980 - 1992; F-80-9-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 80-20)
  - [The Zebra's Pen: collected file], 1984 - 1985; F-80-9-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 80-20)
  - [Outdoor Recreation Centre programs], 1986 - 1988; F-80-9-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 80-20)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1978 - 1979; F-80-9-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 80-20)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1979 - 1980; F-80-9-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 80-20)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1980 - 1981; F-80-9-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 80-20)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1981 - 1982; F-80-9-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 80-20)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1982 - 1983; F-80-9-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 80-20)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1983 - 1984; F-80-9-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 80-20)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1984 - 1985; F-80-9-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1985 - 1986; F-80-9-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1986 - 1987; F-80-9-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1987 - 1988; F-80-9-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1988 - 1989; F-80-9-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1991 - 1992; F-80-9-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1993 - 1994; F-80-9-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
  - [Athletics Yearbook], 1994 - 1995; F-80-9-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
  - Athletics bumper stickers, [197-?]; F-80-9-0-0-88
  - NAIA certificates, 1972 - 1975; F-80-9-0-0-89
  - NAIA certificates, 1976 - 1979; F-80-9-0-0-90
  - NAIA certificates, 1981 - 1985; F-80-9-0-0-91
  - Athletic teams and events posters, 1985 - 1990; F-80-9-0-0-92
  - Athletic teams and events posters, 1991 - 1995; F-80-9-0-0-93
- Sports Information Office files, 1965 - 1994; F-80-10; 96 cm of textual records; Physical description: 81 photographs located in F-80-10-4-1 Physical description: 57 photographs located in F-80-10-4-2 Physical description: 36 photographs located in F-80-10-4-3 Physical description: 57 photographs located in F-80-10-4-4 Physical description: 28 photographs located in F-80-10-4-5 Physical description: 25 photographs located in F-80-10-4-6 Physical description: 16 photographs located in F-80-10-4-7 Physical description: 22 photographs located in F-80-10-4-8 Physical description: 30 photographs located in F-80-10-4-9 Physical description: 5 photographs located in F-80-10-4-10 Physical description: 24 photographs located in F-80-10-4-11 Physical description: 54 photographs located in F-80-10-4-12 Physical description: 23 photographs located in F-80-10-4-13 Physical description: 5 photographs located in F-80-10-4-14 Physical description: 22 photographs located in F-80-10-4-15 Physical description: 21 photographs located in F-80-10-4-16 Physical description: 47 photographs located in F-80-10-4-17 Physical description: 27 photographs located in F-80-10-4-18 Physical description: ca. 90 photographs located in F-80-10-4-19 Physical description: ca. 55 photographs located in F-80-10-4-20 Physical description: 5 photographs located in F-80-10-4-21 Physical description: ca. 80 photographs located in F-80-10-4-22
  The Sports Information Office, reporting to the Director of Athletics, is responsible for implementing promotional activities; liaising with the media, the National Association of Intercollegiate Athletics, and other sports information offices; and the recording of intercollegiate sport statistics and results.
  Series consists of records related to the operations of the Sports Information Office.
  Files within the series appended, ":collected file," indicate an artificial arrangement imposed by a former archivist. Records within these files may have been collected from sources outside the fonds.
  - Sports Information Office files - general, 1970 - 1989; F-80-10-1; 9 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records related to the general operations of the Sports Information Office. Activities and topics documented include athletic award proposals; athletic award banquets and the granting of other honours; departmental reviews; the Coaching Specialist Program; and the recruitment of student athletes. Predominant document types include correspondence, team schedules, proposals, reports, photographs, player profiles, statistics, banquet programs, and a recruiting book.
    Records related to departmental reviews, team schedules, athletic awards, and the Coaching Specialist Program may also be found in the following series: Reports; Intercollegiate Athletic Records; and Workshop and Course Records.
    - Team schedules, 1973 - 1979; F-80-10-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - Resources - proposed materials, 1974; F-80-10-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - National athletes, 1974; F-80-10-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - Department of Athletics Annual Report, 1974; F-80-10-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - Resources - active proposals/prospects, 1975; F-80-10-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - Open house, 1975; F-80-10-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - Athletics review, 1975; F-80-10-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - Review - 10 years, 1975; F-80-10-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - Awards Banquet, 1977; F-80-10-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - [General correspondence], 1977 - 1978; F-80-10-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - Coaching Specialist Program, 1978 - 1979; F-80-10-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - Athlete of the month, [ca 1970] - [ca 1979]; F-80-10-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - [Team schedules], 1981 - 1983; F-80-10-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - [Fall and Spring Varsity Round-Up], 1986 - 1987; F-80-10-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - Bootlegger player of the month, 1988; F-80-10-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - Awards Banquet, 1989; F-80-10-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
    - Recruiting book, [ca 1980] - [ca 1989]; F-80-10-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 80-21)
  - Sports Information Office files - intercollegiate athletics, 1965 - 1994; F-80-10-2; 35 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records related to the operations of the various sports teams that comprise the intercollegiate athletic program. Activities and topics documented include the recording of team statistics and records; team travel; and liaison with the National Association of Intercollegiate Athletics and member universities. Predominant document types include correspondence, rosters, schedules, travel itineraries, statistics, press clippings, news releases, programs (game/meet and season), and newsletters.
    Records related to intercollegiate sports teams may also be found in the following series: Intercollegiate Athletic Records; and Schedules.
    - Basketball season, 1965 - 1966; F-80-10-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1966 - 1967; F-80-10-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1967 - 1968; F-80-10-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1968 - 1969; F-80-10-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1970 - 1971; F-80-10-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1971 - 1972; F-80-10-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1972 - 1973; F-80-10-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1973 - 1974; F-80-10-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Clan Classic, 1974; F-80-10-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1974 - 1975; F-80-10-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season statistics, 1975 - 1976; F-80-10-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1975 - 1976; F-80-10-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1976 - 1977; F-80-10-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - District I basketball, 1977 - 1978; F-80-10-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1977 - 1978; F-80-10-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball final statistics, 1977 - 1978; F-80-10-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball final statistics, 1977 - 1979; F-80-10-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1978 - 1979; F-80-10-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball final statistics, 1978 - 1979; F-80-10-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1979 - 1980; F-80-10-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball: Jay Triano, 1978 - 1981; F-80-10-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball: player profiles, 1979; F-80-10-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Basketball statistics], 1979 - 1980; F-80-10-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball game summary results, 1979 - 1980; F-80-10-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Basketball game programs], [ca 1970] - [ca 1979]; F-80-10-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1980 - 1981; F-80-10-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1981 - 1982; F-80-10-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Final regular season men's basketball statistics, 1981 - 1982; F-80-10-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Final regular season women's basketball statistics, 1981 - 1982; F-80-10-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1982 - 1983; F-80-10-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball statistics, 1983 - 1984; F-80-10-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball season, 1983 - 1984; F-80-10-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Women's basketball], 1985 - 1986; F-80-10-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Women's basketball, 1986 - 1987; F-80-10-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Basketball final statistics, 1987 - 1988; F-80-10-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Men's basketball preview, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Women's basketball final statistics, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Men's basketball - general, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Men's basketball final statistics, 1988 - 1989; F-80-10-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Women's basketball prospectus, 1988 - 1989; F-80-10-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Women's basketball statistics], 1988 - 1991; F-80-10-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Men's basketball information, 1989; F-80-10-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Men's basketball statistics], 1989 - 1992; F-80-10-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Men's basketball statistics], 1992 - 1994; F-80-10-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Women's basketball statistics], 1993 - 1994; F-80-10-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Field hockey, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Women's field hockey], 1992; F-80-10-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Football game records, 1965 - 1980; F-80-10-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - All-time football statistics, [ca 1965] - [ca 1981]; F-80-10-2-0-49 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - All-Americans - football, [ca 1965] - [ca 1987]; F-80-10-2-0-50 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Football statistics - season end by year, 1966 - 1975; F-80-10-2-0-51 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Football, 1969; F-80-10-2-0-52 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Football] statistics, 1970; F-80-10-2-0-53 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Football statistics], 1974; F-80-10-2-0-54 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Football statistics and roster, 1975; F-80-10-2-0-55 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Football statistics, 1975; F-80-10-2-0-56 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Football, 1976; F-80-10-2-0-57 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Football statistics], 1976 - 1977; F-80-10-2-0-58 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Football] statistics, 1977; F-80-10-2-0-59 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Football, 1977; F-80-10-2-0-60 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Football player profiles, 1979; F-80-10-2-0-61 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Football final statistics, 1979 - 1980; F-80-10-2-0-62 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Football roster, 1979 - 1980; F-80-10-2-0-63 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Football], 1980; F-80-10-2-0-64 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Shrum Bowl, 1982; F-80-10-2-0-65 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Football yearly final statistics, 1982 - 1983; F-80-10-2-0-66 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - [Football rosters], 1983 - 1990; F-80-10-2-0-67 (Archival box - standard 80-22)
    - Football final statistics, 1984 - 1989; F-80-10-2-0-68 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Football], 1986; F-80-10-2-0-69 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Football statistics], 1986 - 1988; F-80-10-2-0-70 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Football, 1987; F-80-10-2-0-71 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Football statistics, 1987; F-80-10-2-0-72 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Football], 1987 - 1988; F-80-10-2-0-73 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - SFU and CFL, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-74 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Football, 1989; F-80-10-2-0-75 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Football statistics, 1990; F-80-10-2-0-76 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Football statistics], 1991; F-80-10-2-0-77 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Football statistics], 1991; F-80-10-2-0-78 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Football defensive statistics], 1992; F-80-10-2-0-79 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Football], 1993; F-80-10-2-0-80 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Golf, 1990 - 1991; F-80-10-2-0-81 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Golf, 1992; F-80-10-2-0-82 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Parachuting, 1974 - 1976; F-80-10-2-0-83 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Rowing, 1974; F-80-10-2-0-84 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Rowing, 1974 - 1978; F-80-10-2-0-85 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Diachem Ski Cup, 1988 - 1989; F-80-10-2-0-86 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Ski team], 1992; F-80-10-2-0-87 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Soccer history, 1975 - 1988; F-80-10-2-0-88 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - History of SFU soccer, 1975 - 1988; F-80-10-2-0-89 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Soccer alumni team, [ca 1980]; F-80-10-2-0-90 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Soccer results, 1987; F-80-10-2-0-91 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Soccer player selection, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-92 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Soccer information, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-93 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Soccer results - Far West Classic, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-94 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Diachem Bowl, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-95 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Soccer nationals, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-96 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Soccer nationals, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-97 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Women's soccer], 1988 - 1992; F-80-10-2-0-98 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Men's soccer], 1988 - 1992; F-80-10-2-0-99 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - Women's soccer, 1990; F-80-10-2-0-100 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Women's softball], 1991 - 1992; F-80-10-2-0-101 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Swimming: official meet results: collected file], 1969; F-80-10-2-0-102 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Swimming: official meet results: collected file], 1965 - 1968; F-80-10-2-0-103 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Swimming: official meet results: collected file], 1970; F-80-10-2-0-104 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Swimming: official meet results: collected file], 1970 - 1971; F-80-10-2-0-105 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Swimming: official meet results: collected file], 1971 - 1972; F-80-10-2-0-106 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Swimming: official meet results: collected file], 1972 - 1973; F-80-10-2-0-107 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Swimming: official meet results: collected file], 1974 - 1975; F-80-10-2-0-108 (Archival box - standard 80-23)
    - [Swimming: official meet results: collected file], 1975 - 1976; F-80-10-2-0-109 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - [Swimming: official meet results: collected file], 1976 - 1977; F-80-10-2-0-110 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - [Swimming: official meet results: collected file], 1977 - 1978; F-80-10-2-0-111 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - [Swimming: official meet results: collected file], 1979 - 1980; F-80-10-2-0-112 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - Swimming: NAIA championship program, 1980; F-80-10-2-0-113 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - Swimming: NAIA national swim results, 1981; F-80-10-2-0-114 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - [NAIA swimming and diving championships], 1981 - 1982; F-80-10-2-0-115 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - [Swimming: official meet results: collected file], 1981 - 1982; F-80-10-2-0-116 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - [Swimming: official meet results: collected file], 1983 - 1984; F-80-10-2-0-117 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - Clan swim results, 1988 - 1989; F-80-10-2-0-118 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - Track records, 1970 - 1987; F-80-10-2-0-119 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - Track: cross country, 1986 - 1987; F-80-10-2-0-120 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - Cross country, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-121 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - Track and field, cross country results, 1991 - 1992; F-80-10-2-0-122 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - Track and field nationals, 1992; F-80-10-2-0-123 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - Volleyball results, 1980 - 1981; F-80-10-2-0-124 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - Volleyball results, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-125 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - Women's volleyball, 1988; F-80-10-2-0-126 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - [Women's volleyball statistics], 1989 - 1993; F-80-10-2-0-127 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - Wrestling, 1981 - 1982; F-80-10-2-0-128 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - Wrestling, 1987 - 1988; F-80-10-2-0-129 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - [Wrestling programs and results], 1988 - 1989; F-80-10-2-0-130 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
  - Sports Information Office files - publications and publicity, 1973 - 1993; F-80-10-3; 17 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records related to the publications and publicity of the intercollegiate athletics program. Activities and topics documented include the production of game and season programs and other informational publications; the tracking of media coverage of SFU teams; and the issuing of news releases. Predominant document types include news releases, press clippings, programs (game/event and season), press guides, and public relations and promotions guidelines.
    Records related to publications and publicity may also be found in the following series: Intercollegiate Athletic Records; Workshop and Course Records; and Publication and Publicity Records.
    - SFU Sport-O-Grams, 1975 - 1976; F-80-10-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - News releases, 1975 - 1978; F-80-10-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - [Shrum Bowl news release], 1989; F-80-10-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - [Basketball news releases], 1993; F-80-10-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - [Basketball press clippings], 1975 - 1976; F-80-10-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - [Men's basketball press clippings], 1988 - 1989; F-80-10-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 80-24)
    - [Football press clippings], 1988; F-80-10-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Shrum Bowl press clippings], 1988; F-80-10-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Olympic press clippings], 1988; F-80-10-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Soccer, track and field, women's sports, and wrestling press clippings], 1975 - 1976; F-80-10-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Soccer press clippings], 1979 - 1980; F-80-10-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Soccer press clippings], 1980 - 1981; F-80-10-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Soccer Training Centre press clippings], 1988; F-80-10-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Field hockey, women's soccer, volleyball, cross country, swimming, and skiing press clippings], 1988; F-80-10-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Wrestling press clippings], 1988; F-80-10-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - Basketball season programs, 1975 - 1991; F-80-10-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - Soccer season programs, 1978; F-80-10-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Working material for 1982 NAIA swimming and diving championship program], F-80-10-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Wrestling season programs], 1986; F-80-10-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Football game programs], 1973 - 1988; F-80-10-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - Programs - games at home, 1974 - 1976; F-80-10-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Football season programs], 1975 - 1979; F-80-10-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Football season programs], 1981 - 1990; F-80-10-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - Soccer press material, 1977 - 1980; F-80-10-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Track and field championship program], 1989; F-80-10-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - Wrestling press guides, 1979 - 1980; F-80-10-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - [Public Relations and Promotions Guideline], 1976; F-80-10-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 80-25)
    - Athletics: Public Relations and Promotions Guideline, [ca 1980] - [ca 1989]; F-80-10-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 80-26)
    - Christmas card [football team photograph], 1973; F-80-10-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 80-26)
  - Sports Information Office files - photographs, 1971 - 1993; F-80-10-4; 36 cm of textual records 29.5 cm of photographic material
    Subseries consists of photographs. Activities and topics documented include participation of SFU teams in intercollegiate games and events; and team membership. Predominant document types include black & white and colour photographs of various sizes, negatives, and contact sheets.
    Textual records; Photographic materials
    Photographs may also be found in the following series: Intercollegiate Athletic Records; and Recreational Club Records.
    - Men's basketball, 1986 - 1987; F-80-10-4-0-1; 81 photographs (Archival box - standard 80-26)
    - Women's basketball, 1986 - 1987; F-80-10-4-0-2; 57 photographs (Archival box - standard 80-26)
    - Women's basketball, 1987 - 1988; F-80-10-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 80-26)
    - Women's basketball, 1988 - 1989; F-80-10-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 80-26)